[
    {
        "front": "けんこう",
        "back": "health",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "まず",
        "back": "first of all",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "あぶら",
        "back": "fat",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "だめ",
        "back": "should not",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "ジョギンング",
        "back": "jogging",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "いじょう",
        "back": "over",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "いか",
        "back": "under",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "いがい＜ー＞いない",
        "back": "except; in addition<->within",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうかん",
        "back": "habit",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "けっして（～ない）",
        "back": "never",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "つづける",
        "back": "to continue (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～が）つづく",
        "back": "to continue (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうぶん",
        "back": "enough",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "きそう",
        "back": "to invite",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "はじめる",
        "back": "to start",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "おどろく",
        "back": "to be surprised",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "マラソン",
        "back": "marathon",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "よてい",
        "back": "schedule",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    },
    {
        "front": "はずかしい",
        "back": "to be embarrassed",
        "chapter": "N4 C30"
    }
]